Benjamin Boswick

Master of Landscape Architecture Candidate

A hard-working individual who effectively prioritizes tasks, operating in both independent and group settings. With intense dedication towards academics, a consistent work ethic is displayed. Keeping an open mind is necessary for creativity and retaining new information and experiences in the field.

Contact Information

Address

840 Ash Street

Winnipeg, MB R3N OR8

Phone

(204) 794-9837

Email

ben.boswick@gmail.com

Website

https://boswick.design

References

Available upon request.

Hard Skills

Microsoft Office

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Photoshop

Rhino3D

TwinMotion

VectorWorks

AutoCAD

QGIS

Adobe Illustrator

SketchUp

Adobe Premiere Pro

Lumion

Education

Present

^{2021/09} - M.L.Arch., University of Manitoba

2018/09 -2021/05

B. Env.D., University of Manitoba

2016/09 -2018/05

University 1/Faculty of Science, University of Manitoba

Experience

Current

^{2023/05} Design Intern

The Nadi Group (289 Garry Street - Suite #300)

2022/10

2022/07 - • Design and research support for various projects and initiatives

Executed assigned contract adminstration tasks

• Aided landscape architects and planners in design process

Fulfilled on-site observation and documention

2024/01 -Current

Research Assistant

U.M. Faculty of Architecture - Department of Landscape Architecture (Yuhao Lu)

Complete assigned cumulative research tasks

• Contribute information and feedback toward collaborative documents

2022/09 -Current

Teaching Assistant

U.M. Faculty of Architecture - Landscape & Urbanism Studio 5 (EVLU 4012 - Fall '22. '23) U.M. Faculty of Architecture - Ecology & Design II (EVLU 3004 - Fall '22, Winter '24)

Provide technical tutorials to students for various relevant programs

Participation in and respond with feedback during project reviews

• Prepare technical files for student use in studio projects

2015/02 -2022/07

Sales Associate

McMunn and Yates Building Supplies (600 Pembina Highway)

• Created and managed sales orders through a Point of Sales system

• Developed quotes for various products and structural packages

• Direct customer service and tactful handling of challenging situations

Attained knowledge of an array of products in every department

Associations Soft Skills

Communication

Collaboration

Interpersonal Skills

Time Management

Estimation

Dedication

Problem Solving

Merchandising

2020-22 Student Mentor and Ambassador

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Partners Program

Providing advice and guidance to peers

Participating as a faculty representative in various events

2020-21 **Graduation Committee Treasurer**

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Student Architecture Society

Managing committee finances

Communicating and maintaining faculty wear inventory

2019-24 Student Affiliate

Manitoba Association of Landscape Architects (MALA)